Go home and shut all the windows because Abigail is coming!
回家把所有窗户都关上，因为阿比盖尔要来了！
In this case, Abigail is not a very angry lady, but the name of a storm chosen by the public in an initiative by the UK weather service, the Met Office, and its Irish counterpart Met Eireann.
这一次，她不是一位怒气冲冲的女士，而是一场风暴的名字，这个名字是英国气象局（Met Office）及其爱尔兰对应机构爱尔兰气象服务局（Met Eireann）发起的一项活动中由公众选出的。
In the last few months they have compiled a list of names suggested by ordinary people.
在过去的几个月里，他们编撰了一份由民众提议的名字清单。
In alphabetical order, Barney is next, followed by Clodagh.
按字母的顺序排列，接下来是巴尼（Barney），然后是克洛达（Clodagh）。
You might find Katie down the line, and also Nigel.
你可能还会在名单中看到凯蒂（Katie），还有奈杰尔（Nigel）。
The idea of giving peoples' names to storms is to make people more aware that bad weather is on its way – and it is more understandable than giving them the latitude and longitude.
给风暴起人名的想法是为了让人们更加意识到恶劣天气即将来临——而且这比告诉他们风暴的经纬度更容易理解。
Following a convention by the US, no storms will be given names beginning with the less common letters: Q, U, X, Y and Z.
遵循美国的惯例，不会用不太常见的字母（Q、U、X、Y和Z）开头的名字给风暴命名。
The National Hurricane Center in Miami has officially been naming the Atlantic's tropical cyclones since 1953 – men's names were included in the 1970s.
自1953年以来，位于迈阿密的美国国家飓风中心就已经正式为大西洋上的热带气旋命名了—— 20世纪70年代开始纳入了男性的名字。
But the list is maintained and updated by the World Meteorological Organization, a UN agency based in Geneva.
但这份名单由世界气象组织进行维护和更新，这是一家总部位于日内瓦的联合国机构。
Names of storms considered too catastrophic are 'retired' and replaced.
被认为灾难性过于严重的风暴名字会被“退役”并替换掉。
No more Katrina – the name of the devastating hurricane that killed nearly 2,000 in the US in 2005.
不会再有卡特里娜（Katrina）这个名字了——这是2005年那场在美国造成近2000人死亡的毁灭性飓风的名字。
Cyclones are upgraded to hurricanes if they reach 119km/h.
如果气旋的风速达到每小时119公里，就会升级为飓风。
But what happens when there are too many storms in the world in a particular year?
但是，如果在某一年里世界上出现了太多的风暴会怎么样呢？
Julian Heming, tropical predictions scientist at the Met Office in the UK, explains: "If the remainder of the season is very active, it's not out of the question we'll have to… start using letters from the Greek alphabet."
英国气象局的热带气象预测科学家朱利安・赫明（Julian Heming）解释说：“如果这个季节的剩余时间里风暴活动仍然非常频繁，那么我们不得不……开始使用希腊字母表中的字母（来命名风暴）也不是不可能的。”